Sometimes I wonder...
how I got to be the way I am.
Most fathers have big dreams
for their little girls.
For me, it was to become a concert pianist.
But life never turns out the way we expect.
And when we moved to hong kong...
everything changed.
My father was an important businessman.
I never knew exactly
what he did for a living...
but we always moved around a lot.
For me, home was always where my family was.
Ah.
hi.
huh?
ho! Okay.
As the years went by...
a new love brought me closer to my father...
the art of Wushu.
he was very proud.
Growing up was like a dream.
But nothing lasts forever.
- Good night, sir.
- Good night.
Balrog.!
- papa.! papa.!
- Chun-Li.!
- Where you going?
- Get off me!
- Let her go.
- Let me go!
I love what you've done to your new place.
Next time you move, tell me...
I'll bring you a housewarming gift.
Papa!
- Let me go!
- Well, well, Balrog. It seems we have a wild one here.
Let her go, Bison.
Shh. It's okay, my sweet.
A gentleman would never harm a schoolgirl.
Go.
Bye-bye.
Night-night.
Balrog.
Chun-Li!
No.!
hey! You leave her alone!
Get in there!
Thank you very much.
Now I remember why no one wanted to play
with you atJuilliard.
- Aren't you so sweet.
- I'm serious.
You always get the flowers.
So how's your mom? Did she come?
- No. She's not doing very well.
- Oh.
I'm so sorry.
Oh! I almost forgot.
- This came for you.
- Who's it from?
I don't know. An admirer maybe?
I wonder what it says.
Wow!
- It's beautiful.
- Yeah, it is.
So, after the concert,
I finally gave him my phone number.
I don't know if he'll call but...
- You sure you don't want a ride?
- I'm okay. I like taking the subway.
- I'll call you tomorrow.
- Okay. Okay.
- Bye.
The crime rate continues to rise...
in several slum districts
throughout Southeast Asia.
No single group has been identified
for this new wave of violence.
Authorities instead suggest an overlap...
Chun-Li?
Why did you take off your concert dress?
I couldn't wear it all the way home.
I wanted to see you in it.
And I'll bet you took the subway again, huh?
It's dangerous out there, sweetie.
Mama...
we can't just change our lives...
every time the news tells us so.
Just like your father.
Always standing up when standing's not easy.
Gentlemen, thankyou for coming.
As the distinguished leaders
of the Shadaloo Investment Corporation...
You're all very important men.
And I don't mean to waste your time.
So, a toast.
Over the years our networks
have been very useful for each other.
We've all been well compensated for it.
Unfortunately for you,
that compensation is about to come to an end.
I'm taking over Shadaloo
and moving my interests...
into Bangkok.
Now, I understand that many of these
territories overlap with neighborhoods...
that, at this moment,
You consider to be your own.
This is no longer true.
The sooner you accept this,
the better it'll be.
Show your loyalty to me right now...
and we'll have no problems.
Slainte.
Gentlemen, thank you for your time.
- Nobody talks to me like that.
- Who the hell does he think he is?
That pig.
Mmm. Mmm-mm.
This just came in.
Gangland homicide?
I love this job.
You're the Interpol man?
Yeah. Call me Nash.
Maya Sunee, Bangkok G.h.
New Year's come early?
We got a tip at 6:00 this morning.
Someone wanted us to know this was here.
heads of every crime family.
Signed, sealed and delivered.
Yeah, Last Supper.
And he serves 'em their own heads.
"he"?
Tell me something I don't know, Nash.
You just inherited a big problem.
Good morning.
Or is it evening?
She had a piano concert.
From what I've heard,
she was quite well received.
You know, I'm surprised you chose
the landscape setting.
I'd have thought of you
as being much more of a big city man.
A prison is a prison, Bison.
No matter what's outside.
Show a prisoner the world, and all he sees...
are the bars on the window.
You needn't be so cynical.
Ahhh. home, sweet home.
- Gorgeous, isn't it?
- So how'd your meeting go?
Very well. Thank you for asking.
I'm officially the only surviving
partner of Shadaloo.
Now we move on to
the Bangkok board of directors.
I'll need their contacts for that.
killing them isn't gonna
get you anywhere, Bison.
I'm not interested in the board.
I'm interested in their families.
Damn you!
Get him more pictures of the girl,
something more upbeat this time.
It's amazing what a man will do
just to see his daughter.
There's one thing I learned in the slums...
When people are hungry,
there's nothing they won't do.
Everyone has a price.
With my mother gone,
the path in front of me was empty.
I couldn't help feeling
like I was being led somewhere new.
Was this mysterious scroll a message?
Who was it from?
I had to find out.
Crashing our party?
Get used to it.
We're your new roommates.
Who says we need any?
I've spent the last three years of my life...
chasin' around an organization
called Shadaloo.
- Shadaloo's a myth.
- I wouldn't be in this ashtray if it was.
Those bodies piled up in the harbor...
they were the heads of the ruling
crime families of Bangkok, correct?
- Yes.
- Uh-huh. Right?
And now they're all dead except for one.
his name's Bison...
and I've tracked him through 11 major cities
on four continents and never come close.
Not once.
This guy walks through the raindrops.
And anybody that's against him
is either dead or on their way.
Now he's the last man standing.
So, where do we start?
You don't want a ticket
to this dance, Detective.
You've never even seen me dance.
To find Gen...
I was told I had to leave behind
the life I knew...
even my home...
and all the memories that were so dear to me.
As it was written in the scroll...
I had to forget everything I used to be.
I had to lose myself
to the pulse of the streets.
I had to become one
with the people of Bangkok.
This was all so new to me.
Life was hard on these streets.
Every night was a struggle.
Every meal was a gift.
Day after day, I searched for Gen.
As time went by,
I was getting further and further away...
from all that I ever was.
I felt lost...
chasing a ghost I might never find.
But what I found...
I wasn't prepared for.
Everywhere I looked...
there was crime without punishment.
I wanted to do something.
Anything.
I just didn't know where to begin.
Who could protect these people?
Who was oppressing them?
Fantastic, isn't it?
All these waterfront slums
will soon belong to Shadaloo.
Location, location, location.
This came in from Murmansk.
I think you're gonna like it.
It's the White Rose.
how long has it been? Fifteen years?
Seventeen years...
four months and six days.
Bring the package to Bangkok... safely.
There is no room for error.
I got some bad news too.
The schoolgirl's gone.
We thinkshe's in Bangkok.
But don't worry. We'll find her.
hey!
Leave him alone.
It's none of your business, baby.
Where you go, trouble follows.
My name is Gen. Don't worry, Chun-Li.
- how do you know who I am?
- We've been watching you for some time.
I know who took your father.
he's alive? Where is he?
- I'll tell you when you're ready.
- Ready for what?
Ready to put away your anger.
You are the only one who can bring
your father back, and I can help you do it.
But you have to do it my way.
Just tell me where he is.
You don't know what you're up against.
Let me show you.
These are the slums.
The people are suffering.
The streets are being taken over
by a criminal organization...
called Shadaloo.
I used to be a part of'em.
When you fight on the side of monsters,
eventually you become one yourself.
That's why I changed, saw the better way.
The Order of the Web.
I created the Order to fight injustice...
to protect the people
who can't fight for themselves.
- What does this have to do with my father?
- Everything.
Your father was a very
well-connected businessman.
his relationships could open any doors
in any country anywhere.
Many people wanted those connections.
People like Bison, the leader of Shadaloo.
My father would never help someone like that.
No? Not even for the safety
of his only daughter?
- What do you want from me?
- I'm giving you a chance to join us...
to become part of the Web, to fight
for something far greater than yourself.
I already know how to fight.
Impress me.
Anger isn't gonna guide you.
Trust me. I know.
- Why are you mad right now?
- Because you're hurting me.
No. You're hurting yourself.
You fight with passion...
but your anger distorts your judgment.
Bison will see right through you.
Believe in your true self.
Look for an innocence beyond the anger.
You still got a long way to go.
Bison, the same man who tookmy father...
was here in Bangkok.
I'd never been so close...
and so far away.
I had to research his organization.
I had to find out about Shadaloo.
I must congratulate you all, gentlemen.
You've shown remarkably sound judgment.
Not many municipal governments
would take such a bold stand...
against the criminal elements
of their own population.
People will point to you
long after your time has passed.
And here's the best part...
your debts are now clean.
What about our families?
Your children have been returned.
Mr. Bison thanks you
for your continuing support.
The papers are signed.
The slums are in your hands.
Good girl, Cantana.
I'll handle the Secretary of Commerce.
Looks like somebody's about to own
the Ministry of Commerce.
Nash, I have a source at the port authority.
he said the state just sold the majority share
of the slums to Esperanto Security Company.
Everything from the harbor to the markets.
Of course. It's a front for Shadaloo.
Bison's bringing crime into the neighborhoods
to drive the land value down.
And then he's buying it back up wholesale.
- We gotta move on then.
- Okay, we're on it. Come with me.
Isn't this your old neighborhood?
Old and new.
home, sweet home.
I'm such a sentimental guy
that I invested in this shit hole.
Though I have to admit,
I got a very nice deal on it.
It doesn't look like a nice deal for them.
And I think they want it back.
Too late for that.
Bulldozers come in tomorrow.
And soon after...
beautiful homes for those who can afford it.
I'm making Bangkok a better place.
- They should build me a temple for that.
- Mmm.
Life's about choices, Balrog.
I was about his age when I made mine.
And I've never looked back.
hey, Maya?
I love stakeouts as much as the next guy...
but what the hell are we doing here?
Well, our source says Bison's guy...
should be leaving
for the meet any second now.
Are you sure we're in the right place?
No, I just like the view.
Wait. There he is.
Come here.
- That had to be done.
- Yeah, it had to.
There goes the Benz.
Just make sure you don't lose him, Romeo.
Yeah, yeah. I'm on it.
Why are we meeting here? We handed over
the slums. What more do you want?
There's a package coming in
on a ship from Murmansk.
We need safe passage and no damn customs.
You're the commerce secretary.
So make it happen.
- I need details.
- It's on the shipping manifest.
The package is called the White Rose.
Only in the dark do all colors become one.
You can't just cope with the darkness...
You have to embrace what is without fear.
You have to feel without your senses.
harness the energy around you.
Well done. Let's eat.
Yo, Maya. You almost done in there?
hey, it's not my fault you got here early.
So we're going clubbing tonight.
Bison's attache loves
hittin' the nightlife...
and I want to see what she's up to.
Always work with you.
You know, Nash,
if what you say about Bison is true...
waiting and watching his bitch
is not gonna be the way we bring him down.
We should be more aggressive.
Looks like you got that down.
Well, unlike you, I don't lose my man.
And besides,
there's nothing I won't try once.
Do you have any cash? I'm thirsty.
- Are you serious?
- I don't have any money.
You should try hocking those gold handcuffs.
To the boys who have got my back.
Tonight, I've got my own. Enjoy.
Thought I might ask you a few questions.
Tell me about the White Rose.
You must be Daddy's little girl.
Out of order, ladies.
- Cantana.
- I know who your boss is.
- Tell me.
- It's a shipment.
Arrives at the end of the month...
the last Friday.
- Where?
- Central Shipyard, Berth 21.
I want you to send Bison a message.
Tell him the schoolgirl's grown up.
This is it.
Nash... Nash, something's going down.
hey.!
Interpol.! Freeze.! Stay down.
Are you gonna tell me, or should I guess?
Go ahead and guess.
That is one tough cookie.
She most certainly was.
But she'd said enough.
The damage was done.
You think we gotta change the plans?
Unfortunately, we do.
Get the insurance policy.
Call Vega.
- I don't know. Maybe she's an angry stripper.
- Yeah.
An irate pole dancer
not happy with her tips...
sets off Armageddon.
- keep spitballing that, Maya. I love where your head's at.
- All right, Nash.
What do you think it is?
This girl just wiped the floor with some
of the most dangerous players in Bangkok...
and then bails out like
she's got a plane to catch.
She's making a statement.
Now, come on, fellas. Who is this girl?
Does she have priors?
A paper trail? how about a name?
We checked the archives.
Nash, she's off the radar.
We can look at
the closed-circuit security feed.
The front door has a good shot.
hey, thanks.
Mmm-mm.
how's aggressive workin' for ya?
Shut up.
- No one's talking.
- No, they won't.
They're protecting her.
You're right.
- home-cooked.
- Tell me about Bison.
We grew up together.
Like me, he was a criminal...
with no future.
his parents were Irish missionaries...
who died in Thailand when he was very young.
Soon, the boy became very ill.
Where he was, no one cared about the sick.
So they left him... to die.
But the child survived.
With each passing year...
he became more and more feared...
and a well-known thief on the streets.
he took what he wanted when he wanted it.
But even that wasn't enough.
he yearned for more.
So he went to the darkcaves
in the phang Nga Bay...
and brought his new wife.
From ancient tales...
he'd heard about the darkforces...
that could free a man from his conscience.
he had to transfer
the goodness ofhis soul...
into his unborn daughter.
The transformation was complete.
he had finally rid himself ofhis conscience.
Now he's home again...
Bangkok, where it all started.
he's making moves on a bigger scale
than I've ever seen before.
Sounds like the perfect time
to take him down and bring my father back.
how's your wrist?
- It's better.
- Good.
You're doing well.
Chun-Li.
I've got an important task for you.
Maybe the hardest thing
I'll ever ask you to do.
I want you to go buy groceries for breakfast.
Pawning off all the hard work?
That's the privilege of a teacher.
Get the R.P.G.
Fire the missile!
Give me that! I'll do it myself.
Say good night, baby.
Let's go.
I called you because
you do my best dirty work.
Something very important
to me is about to arrive in Bangkok.
And I don't want anything to
interfere with it.
There is a schoolgirl
that needs taking care of.
What kind of schoolgirl are we talking about?
She is a problem child.
Well, well, well.
She'll never be a problem again.
You've got ghosts. Let's see 'em.
Chun-Li.
huh?
No wonder you wear a mask.
I'd hide that face too.
You bitch!
I'll cut you open!
You think this is over?
No. I'm just getting started.
This is a restricted area.
I thought you might make an exception.
I have a question for you.
A shipment was scheduled
to arrive at Berth 21 in two days.
Listen, lady,
I think it's time for you to go.
They call it bai mei... the White Rose.
What time does it arrive?
Midnight.
You should learn some manners.
Never put your hands on a lady.
Forget to pay the rent? Where is everybody?
Orders from up high. We're off the case.
What orders?
Orders, Nash.
You were right.
Shadaloo is very well connected.
- We're out.
- hey, wait a minute. Maya.
That's it?
I'm sorry, Charlie.
You're not a schoolgirl anymore.
Bring her in.
Oh.
So this is the girl that roughed up Vega?
I like her already.
huang!
Let me go!
papa.
You two take some time and catch up.
Chun-Li.
Why?
Papa, I had to.
You know I tried so hard for so many years...
just to keep you safe...
to protect you...
to make sure you had the good life.
I would rather have you.
Getting in Bison's way, it's a losing battle.
Why are you doing this to yourself?
Sometimes, you have to stand up...
when standing isn't easy.
- You taught me that.
- I love you so much.
I love you.
I love family reunions.
Don't touch her.
If you touch her again,
You get nothing more from me.
- Do you understand?
- Oh, I understand.
You see,
Your father has been the milk of my business.
But even milk...
has an expiration date.
- No. No, don't.
- I'm a man of my word.
- No, please! - I promised him
he'd have a chance to say good-bye.
No! No! No, please, stop!
No!
You... will not stop me.
Take the body away.
Balrog.
Is there anything you wanna say before
we get this over with?
All right.
And make it quick.
Should we kill you
before or after we cut you?
I wouldn't do either.
- You're not in a place to negotiate.
- Not yet.
Swing around the block.
Ow!
Somebody got a problem?
Come on! Come on! Let's go!
You're alive.
Come on.
Gen.
Where you go...
trouble certainly does follow.
Let me see this.
hmm. Let's fix it.
Come.
Pretty soon,
You're not gonna need me anymore.
Now, let's find the White Rose.
how's your arm doing?
I'm sorry. They made me do it.
Do you remember my question,
or do I have to ask you again?
Tomorrow night, a ship from Murmansk...
will arrive in the front berth.
You wouldn't set me up twice now, would you?
Please. Look.
It's right here. See?
Thank you.
Sorry for interrupting.
No problem.
hi.
What can I do for ya?
Bison's shipment arrives
at Central harbor tomorrow night.
And?
I'm gonna need backup.
Unit three's holding. Got it.
Check the ammo.
Good. We're good to go.
All right, Bison, where the hell are you?
- We've got guests, fellas.
- We're set.
I thought you were out.
We all grew up in this neighborhood.
Don't wanna see it disappear.
Looks like they're expecting us.
We are not alone.
It makes no difference. We're ready.
Bomb! Everybody out! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go!
Nash!
- Stay low!
- Come on! Come on!
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Are you okay?
Okay. Just stay here.
You know,
You're a lot slower than you used to be.
And you're just as ugly as I remember!
Where's the White Rose?
You don't even know what the White Rose is!
By the time you fools figure it out,
she'll be long gone.
"She"?
You two stay with her! You, come with me!
That's Bison.
Give me a fix on the helicopter
leaving my location.
Nash, out.
Gen.!
The White Rose...
not a weapon. A girl.
A girl? I just saw her.
Bison's daughter was
the conduit for his soul.
- he rid himself ofhis goodness
by passing it into her.
And she is his only weakness.
That's why he's been
looking for her all this time.
- Yeah.
- Okay, let's go.
And I'm gonna need support when we get there!
Don't keep me waiting! Nash, out!
We got him on radar! We gotta move now!
- Bison's got a girl with him.
- What girl?
- his daughter. her name's Rose.
- Let's get her.
Okay.
Move!
Ah.
Still no word from Balrog.
If anything happens to her...
I'll kill you first.
Where's the girl?
hello, old friend.
You should never have left the team.
We wouldn't be standing here like this.
But, of course,
only one of us is standing.
Nice try.
Seven-six-seven-five.
You must be Rose.
hello, old friend.
Where is she?
It's time we said good-bye,
old friend.
Fathers always have a soft spot
for their daughters.
That's how I brought yours down.
You didn't think this was
going to end well, now, did you?
Chun-Li.!
You know what you need to do.
Fathers always have a weakness
for their daughters.
Chun-Li.
Nice work.
hey, you'd better get out of here.
Chopper's on the other side of the island.
I never saw you.
See to it she gets a real life.
You too, huh?
Thanks, Nash.
Charlie Nash, Interpol! hold your fire!
hey.
- You're back in business, huh?
- Yep.
Are you sure you wanna go back
to Gangland homicide?
- It's what I do.
- It's your first time?
Nah. I've been there before.
I can imagine.
If you get lonely at night, don't call me.
I love this job.
I don't think
this was the life my father envisioned for me.
But... maybe it was.
I know he would have been proud.
I've stood when standing was not easy...
and have found something to believe in.
Something worth fighting for.
The Order of the Web.
Gen!
There's more work to be done.
Something about this smells of an old friend.
- But Bison's dead.
- We need to recruit.
They've been talking about
a fighter in Japan...
Ryu... something.
I hear he's a force to be reckoned with.
Wanna come?
Maybe next time.
Does this mean you're done fighting?
No. For now, I'm home.
Ace... hood.!
hood.! Brother.!
Lookat that.! Shit. hey.
Yeah.